Guide to the Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences Records SC1055
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Administration, 1952-1989; Series 1
  - Robert Sears, Correspondence with CASBS Director, 1963 Apr-1973 Jan (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - George P. Shultz, Correspondence with CASBS Director, 1979 May-1980 Jan (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Neil J. Smelser, Correspondence with CASBS Director, 1979 Feb-1980 Dec (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Patrick Suppes, Correspondence with CASBS Director, 1978 Feb-1981 Aug (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Frank Stanton, Correspondence with CASBS Director, 1963 Feb-1978 Mar (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Ralph Tyler, Correspondence and Writings, 1967 Aug-1981 June (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - O. Meredith Wilson, Correspondence with CASBS Director, 1962 Jan-1979 Nov (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Logan Wilson, Correspondence with CASBS Director, 1963 Apr-1974 Apr (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Paul Herman Buck, Correspondence with CASBS Director, 1959 July-1969 Apr (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Gardner Lindzey Colorado University Honorary Degree and Photo, 1989 Nov 10 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Gardner Lindzey Retirement Celebration, 1989 Apr 29 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Parties
    - CASBS Party - Palo Alto Open House, 1954 Sep 24 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - CASBS Party - Dr. Tyler's Party, 1954 Oct 12 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - CASBS Party - Stanford Open House, 1955 Oct 5 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - CASBS Party - Bonfire Party, 1954 Nov 18 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - CASBS Party - California Party, 1954 Dec 19 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - CASBS Party - Christmas Party, 1954 Dec 15 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - CASBS Party - Mary Tyler, 1955 Oct 14 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - CASBS Party - General Systems Conference, 1955 Feb 26 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - CASBS Party - Opening Party, 1955 Sep 21 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - CASBS Party - American Psychology Association, 1955 Sep 6 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - CASBS Party - Picnic at Paul Masson Winery, 1955 Oct 9 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - CASBS Party - Bonfire Party, 1955 Nov 17 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - CASBS Party - Dean's Dinner, 1955 Nov 9 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - CASBS Party - Christmas Party, 1956 Dec 16 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - CASBS Party - Low Tea Party, 1956 Mar 16 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - CASBS Party - Tea Party, 1956 Apr 6 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - CASBS Party - Alfred Kroeber Party, 1956 June 18 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - CASBS Party - Christmas Party, 1956 Dec 7 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - CASBS Parties, 1957 Jan 16-1957 Sep (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - CASBS Party - Bonfire Party, 1957 Nov 12 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - CASBS Party - Director's Cocktail Party, 1957 Jan 4 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - CASBS Party - Dinner Parties, 1957 Oct-1957 Dec (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - CASBS Party - Dinner and Cocktail Parties, 1958 Jan-1958 Mar (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - CASBS Party - Dinner Parties, 1958 Apr-1958 Nov (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - CASBS Party - Bonfire Party, 1958 Nov 21 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - CASBS Party - Christmas Party, 1958 Dec 15 (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - CASBS Party - Farewell Party for Michael and Joan Young, 1959 Feb 12 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - CASBS Party - Dinner and Talk, Joshua Lederberg, 1959 Apr 6 (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - CASBS Party - Bonfire Party, 1959 Nov 20 (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - CASBS Party - Christmas Party, 1959 Dec 15 (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - CASBS Party - Director's Lunch, 1960 Jan 31, 1960 Apr 10 (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - CASBS Party - Fellows' Farewell Party, 1960 July 27 (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - CASBS Party - Wine Tasting, Wine Buying and Punch Party, 1960 May-1960 Oct (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - CASBS Party - Bonfire Party, 1960 Nov 18 (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - CASBS Party - Christmas Dinner, 1960 Dec 16 (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - CASBS Party - Friday Afternoon Carnival Hour, 1960 Jan 20 (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - CASBS Party - Children's Christmas Party, 1960 Dec 15 (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - CASBS Party - Directors' Lunch, 1961 Feb 3-1961 Apr 21 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - CASBS Party - Picnic at Paul Masson Winery, 1961 Apr 29 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - CASBS Party - Bonfire Party and Christmas Party, 1961 Nov-1961 Dec (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - CASBS Party - Board of Directors' Lunch, 1962 Jan 20 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - CASBS Party - Purim Celebration, 1962 Feb 27 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - CASBS Party - Trustees' Lunch, 1962 Apr 28 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - CASBS Party - Science Research Association Lunches, 1962 July 27-28 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - CASBS Party - Trustees' Lunch, 1962 Oct 29 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - CASBS Party - Big Game Party, 1962 Nov 23 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - CASBS Party - December Parties, 1962 Dec (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - CASBS Party - Happy Hours, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - CASBS Party - Trustees' Lunches, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - CASBS Party - February, March, October and December Parties, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - CASBS Party - Parties in 1964 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - CASBS Party - Trustees' Parties, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - CASBS Party - Trustees' Lunches, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - CASBS Parties, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - CASBS Party - Trustees' Lunches, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - CASBS Parties, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - CASBS Parties, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - CASBS Parties, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - CASBS Parties, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - CASBS Party - Peg Shoup's Retirement Party, Feb 17, year unknown (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - CASBS Parties, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - D.E. McHenry Committee meeting at CASBS re: American higher education of foreign students, 1962 Apr 30-1962 May 1 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - SSRC Committee on Personality Development in Youth, 1962 May 30 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Navy Project, 1962 July (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Primate Project, 1962 Jan (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Social Science Curriculum Conference - Materials for the Schools, 1962 Dec (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Conference on Componential Analysis, Wenner-Gren Foundation, 1964 June (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Inivtational Work Conference on the Identification and Assessment of Academic Ability and Potential of Children from Culturally Deprived Groups, 1964 Aug (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Insititute of Mathematical Social Science, Academic Governing Board, 1964 Aug 12 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Conference on Perceptual and Linguistic Aspects of Reading Skill, 1964 Oct 31-1964 Nov 2 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Seminar on New Trends in Latin American Research, 1964 Oct 9-1964 Oct 11 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Conference on Comparative Political Development, 1964 Aug 3-1964 Aug 28 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Advanced Research Seminar on Mathematical Models of Economic Growth, 1965 July (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Meetings and Conferences, 1965 Jan-1966 Mar (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - SSRC, Committee on Socialization and Social Structure, 1965 June 14-1965 July 9 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Seminar on Models for Discrimination Learning, 1966 June 27-1966 July 15 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Seminar on Learning and Television, 1966 July (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Conference on Ethics of Medical Education, 1967 June 26 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Conference on Law and the Behavioral Sciences, 1956 July 10 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Singer, Milton Conference, 1957 Sep 10 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Conference of the Study of Cooperative Education, 1959 Dec (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Conference on Policies and Strategy for Strengthening the Curriculum of the American Public Schools, 1959 Jan (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Conference of the Council for the Advancement of Small Colleges, 1959 July-1959 Aug (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - CASBS Cocktail Party Groups, 1958 Jan (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - SSRC, Personality Development in Youth, 1959 Dec (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Thomas Alva Edison Foundation, Conference on Programmed Teaching and the Educational Process, 1960 Dec (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Conference on Human Environments in Central Africa, 1960 July (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - California Extension Conference, 1959 Nov (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - NIH, Behavioral Sciences Study Section, 1961 June (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - SSRC Conferences, 1961 Feb-1961 June (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Seminar on Latin American Studies, 1963 July 8-1963 Aug 23 (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - ACLS Summer Workshop in the Theory of Communist Systems, 1968 Aug (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Psychology of Inflation Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Conference on Componential and Semantic Analysis, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Science Indicators Conference, 1974 June (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Computers at CASBS, 1969-1981 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - FFRP, Conference on Exchange Between the US and China in Psychiatry and the Neurosciences, 1981 Sep (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Conferences (General), 1971-1981 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Summer Institute, The Nature of Morality and Moral Development, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - Summer Institute, Life Span Human Development, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 63-64)
  - FFRP, Conference Planning, 1981 June (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Summer Institute, Stigma and Interpersonal Relationships, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Summer Institute, Biological Differences and Social Equality, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Atwood Richards, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Bert E. Boothe Memorial, 1972-1974 (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1961-1976 (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - The Commonwealth Fund, 1969-1981 (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - The Danforth Foundation, 1968-1973 (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - E.I. DuPont de Nemours Company, 1970-1973 (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 1977-1981 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Fleischmann Foundation, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation, 1961-1981 (Box 33, Folder 3-5)
  - Foundation for Child Development, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Foundation Managers, Inc., 1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Foundations Fund for Research in Psychiatry, 1960-1981 (Box 33, Folder 8-9)
  - Grant Foundation, 1970-1981 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, 1962-1978 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Howard Foundation, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - IBM, 1969-1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - James Irvine Foundation, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Italian Foundations, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation, 1972-1981 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1969-1981 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Charles F. Kettering Foundation, 1970-1981 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1979-1981 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - John and Mary R. Markle Foundation, 1970-1979 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1969-1981 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Summer Institute, 1977 July 7-1977 Aug 2 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Walter E. Meyer Research Institute of Law, 1960-1969 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Naval Research Office, Department of the Navy, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Charles H. Revson Foundation, 1977-1981 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1962-1981 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Rowland Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1968-1981 (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
  - CASBS Alumni, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - CASBS Alumni Responses to Return Invitations, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - CASBS Annual Report and Brochure, 1976-1981 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - CASBS Blood Bank, 1961-1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees - Membership, 1963-1980 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees - Correspondence to Schedule Meetings, 1971-1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees - Contact Information and Biographies, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees - General, 1963-1979 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Financial, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - CASBS Congratulations on Ford Grant, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1971-1981 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Investments, 1963-1979 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Insurance, 1963-1977 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - CASBS Lease, 1961-1980 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - CASBS General History, 1959-1975 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - CASBS Supplies and Equipment, 1956-1979 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - CASBS Tax Reform, 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Visitors, 1971-1979 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Visitors, Foreign, 1971-1980 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - CASBS Circular Letters, 1970-1979 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - CASBS Correspondence, College Student Personnel Institute, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Computer Graphics, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - CASBS Correspondence, Coopers and Lybrand, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - CASBS Correspondence, Cosmos Club, 1975-1980 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - CASBS Architect, Correspondence and Blueprints, 1963-1975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - CASBS Director's Home, 1965-1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Director Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Department of Education Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Educational Testing Service Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Employee Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - CASBS Potential Staff Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Exchange Visitor Program, 1965-1980 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Fellows and Program Committee, 1974-1980 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Fellows - General Correspondence, 1958-1981 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Fellowships, New Categories, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - CASBS Fire, Fellows and Board Correspondence, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - CASBS Fire, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - CASBS Fire, News Clippings and Correspondence, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - CASBS Fire, Fundraising and Correspondence, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - CASBS Fire, Rebuilding Correspondence, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - CASBS Fiscal Projection, 1975 Nov (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - CASBS Miscellaneous Fundraising, 1965-1981 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - John Gardner Letter, 1968 Apr 8 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Governor's Advisory Committee, 1967 Apr (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - William T. Golden Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Aubrey Grossman Letter, 1971 July 30 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare - Protection of Human Subjects (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Higher Degrees Conferred by Institutions of Higher Learning, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Hoover Institution Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - CASBS Human Resources Committee, 1971 Jan (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - IRS Ruling on Center as Educational Institution, 1956-1971 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Native American Issues and Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Institute for Advanced Study Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Institute for Education Development Correspondence, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Institute of International Education, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Legal Correspondence, 1963-1980 (Box 35, Folder 35-36)
  - CASBS Local Points of Interest and Newsletters, 1955-1972 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Minority PhDs, 1957-1969 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - CASBS Minority Scholars, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - National Commission for Cooperative Education, 1962-1968 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971-1981 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Nominations from Graduate Deans, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  - Nominations from College Presidents, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 8-9)
  - Paul Masson Winery Correspondence, 1958-1972 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Peace Corps Correspondence, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell Co. Accountants Correspondence, 1964-1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Correspondence, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - CASBS Publications Addenda, 1959-1963 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Russian and Czech Sociologists, 1963-1977 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, Gift Project, 1969-1971 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, Gift Project Acknowledgments, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1969-1978 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Study Survey of 1957-58 Fellows, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Preston Cutler Personal Files, incl. Pete Seeger letter, 1957-1963 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Selection of Fellows, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Preston Cutler, Edith Goebel Correspondence, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - A Report on the Behavioral Sciences, University of Chicago, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - "Negotiation and Dispute Resolution," Summer Institute, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - CASBS Manuals and Staff Contact, 1978-1982 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Preston Cutler, O. Meredith Wilson and Gardner Lindzey Correspondence, 1968-1983 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - CASBS Library, 1954-1968 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Class Gift 1968 - Statement for library improvement (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Future of the Center - notes and correspondence, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - CASBS Map, Statistics on Fellows and local populations, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - CASBS Roster of Fellows, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Members of the Advisory Committee, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Activities of the Fellows, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Wine Buying Club, 1958-1979 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - "A Fellow's Progress" lyrics to song performed at Center graduation, 1950s (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Oral histories, 2005-05
    - Litt, Iris track 04-05; Wallerstein, Robert track 06-10; Short, Jim track 11-13, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Dornbusch, Sanford M. track 02-05; Luce, Duncan track 06-09; Kingdon, John track 10-12, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Gottesman, Irving track 02-06; Zwicky, Arnold track 07-09, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Converse, Phil track 05-11; Campos, Joe and Fine, Gary track 12-17, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Langemann, Ellen track 01-02; Sears, David Track 03-06, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Pribram, Karl track 02-04; Damon, Bill track 05-07, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Handler Spitz, Ellen, Lipsitt, Lewis, Leiderman, Herb, interviewer Much, Kathleen, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Henderson, Alan track 01-04, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Rothenberg, Albert track 02-07; Zimbardo, Philip G. track 08-10, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Holtzman, Wayne track 01-02; Vazquez, Josephina Z. track 03-06; MacCoby, Michael track 07-09, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
    - Lamm, Donald, 2005-05; 1 optical disc(s) (Minidisc) (Box 37)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2015-128
  - Program of University Surveys of the Behavioral Sciences, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Program of University Surveys of the Behavioral Sciences, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Fellows' Rosters, Contact Information, Newsletters and Interests by Year, 1954-1976 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Fellows' Rosters, Contact Information, Newsletters and Interests by Year, 1954-1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - List of all Fellows by last name, 1954-1970 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - List of foreign Fellows, 1954-1967 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - List of all Fellows by fields, 1954-1977 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Center Employment Policy, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - California State Library Annual Reports from CASBS Library, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Statements Concerning Program of CASBS, 1954 Feb (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - 1st-96th Board Meeting Minutes only (reprinted), 1954-1982 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - CASBS: Notes Toward a History by Arnold Thackray, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Ralph Tyler article in Educational Researcher, 1990 Dec (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Joseph F. Bennett Memorial Meeting, 1956 May 8 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Preston Cutler Various Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Excerpts Concerning the Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - pamphlet, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Memorandum for Persons Interested in Fellowships, and others, 1974 July (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Time Magazine article reprint on CASBS: "Time to Think", 1959 Nov 2 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Supplement to the Ralph Tyler Collection, 1979-1987 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Press Release: O. Meredith Wilson retires, Gardner Lindzey appointed as new Director, 1974 Aug 12 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Preston Cutler personal - Christmas card greeting, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Clark Kerr, Bernard Berelson Telegrams and letter re: Center site selection, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Center/Foundations' Fund for Research in Psychiatry (FFRP) Program and Conferences lists, 1981-1986 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Ralph Tyler correspondence and memos re: planning CASBS policy invitation lists, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Ralph Tyler and Edwin Huddleson Jr. correspondence re: CASBS budget, 1954 June-Aug (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Center Graduation/Commencement Documents, 1954-1983 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Center Graduation/Commencement Documents, 1954-1983 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Center Opening Day telegrams and correspondence (copies), 1954 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Notes of Tour with Henry Raku - landscape design for CASBS, 1975 Oct 2 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Frank Keegan letter to Preston Cutler, 1982 Feb 12 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - A.H. Halsey paper on CASBS: "Social Science in America and Britain", 1957 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Memos to Fellows, 1954 Jun 3 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - CASBS Selection Procedures, excerpts from the Record, 1953-1960 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Fellows of the Center and their Interests, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Preston Cutler memo to Fellows re: removal of couches, 1957 Mar (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Ralph Tyler Board meeting memo to Fellows, 1957 Dec 2 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - 103rd Board Meeting Minutes and Directors Report, Appendices (Evaluation of Candidates, Social Calendar, Grant Proposal, Carnegie Letter (Structural Constraints on Cognitive Development and Developmental Psychopathology), 1984 April 27-28 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - 107th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, Psychiatry), 1985 Oct 25 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - 108th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, Psychiatry), 1986 Feb 7 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - 108th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, copy 2, 1986 Feb 7 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - 109th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1986 May 2-3 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - 110th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1986 Oct 31 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - 110th Board Meeting Minutes and Directors Report copy 2, 1986 Oct 31 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - 111th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1987 Jan 30 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 111th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report copy 2, 1987 Jan 30 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 112th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1987 May 1-2 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 112th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1987 May 1-2 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - 113th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1987 Oct 30 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - 113th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report copy 2, 1987 Oct 30 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 114th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1988 Jan 22 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - 114th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1988 Jan 22 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 115th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1988 Apr 29 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - 115th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1988 Apr 29 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - 116th Board Meeting Minutes and Director's Report, 1988 Oct 28 (Box 39, Folder 11)